

# KIRAN MS

**GRAPHIC DESIGNER** 

## **Profile**

Hi! I am Kiran

I am self-motivated, hard working and interested in graphic designing. I have worked on infographic, Image editing, illustrations & also with the elarning tools adobe captivate & storyline is inspired by a multidisciplinary background. I have a good design sensitivity with video creation and video editing capability for the task provided and with positive attitude towards my career.

8892273281



kiranmsrinivas96@gmail.com



Vidhyamanyanagar (west), Andrahalli Main Road, Banglore 560023

#### **SKILLS**

- Graphic & web design
- Illustration & drawing
- Advertising & branding
- Motion graphics
- Worked on eLearning tools

#### **TOOLS**

- Adobe illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe audition
- Adobe captivate
- Storyline
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Filmora9

#### CERTIFICATE

Certificate in Graphic Design Zee Institute of Creative Art

#### **Education**

- **GRAPHIC DESIGN** Zee Institute Of Creative Art (2018 -2019)
- B.com SS International University (2014 - 2017) (Distance education)

#### Work experience

- Worked as a graphic designer in FOCUS EDUMATICS (E learning company) as a contract based on May 6th 2019 till Dec 2019
- Started working at MET Technologies as a Graphic designer on 16th Dec 2019 Worked on video creation & illustration till Dec 2020
- Started working at Nuage edutech (formerly Focus Edumatics) E learning company as a full time employee on 7th dec\_2020 till present

### **Roles & responsibilites**

- My daily task to complete work based on the module with Storyline or adobe captivate
- Infographics & Photo editing has to be comleted based on the requirement with the help of illustartor or photoshop
- Worked on kenburn style of videos with some good animations by using After effects